Death runs in the family.
Final Destination Bloodlines is a horror, mystery
film directed by Adam B. Stein.
Plagued by a violent recurring nightmare, college student Stefanie heads home to track down the one person who might
be able to break the cycle and save her family from the grisly demise that inevitably awaits them all.
Stefani Reyes, played by Kaitlyn Santa Juana.
Charlie Reyes, played by Teo Briones.
Darlene Campbell, played by Rya Kihlstedt.
Erik, played by Richard Harmon.
Bobby, played by Owen Patrick Joyner.
Julia, played by Anna Lore.
Final Destination Bloodlines is a 2025 American supernatural horror film directed by Zach
Lipovsky and Adam Stein, and written by Guy Busick and Lori Evans Taylor.
It is the sixth in the Final Destination film series, and stars Kaitlyn Santa Juana as a college student named Stefani Reyes, who inherits visions of a 1969
premonition that averted a deadly skyscraper failure from her dying grandmother Iris, who warns Stefani that Death is coming for their family.
Teo Briones, Richard Harmon, Owen Patrick Joyner, Anna Lore, Brec
Bassinger, and Tony Todd appear in supporting roles.
After the commercial success of the previous film, a sixth film entered
development, described as a re-imagining of the franchise.
In March 2020, series producer Craig Perry said the film
would be set "in the world of first responders".
In January 2022, the film was scheduled for release on the streaming service HBO Max,
with Lipovsky and Stein directing and Busick joining Taylor as co-writer.
In March 2024, Warner Bros.
Pictures announced that the film would instead receive a theatrical release.
Filming took place in Vancouver from March to May 2024,
following delays caused by the SAG-AFTRA strike.
Final Destination Bloodlines was released in the United
States on May 16, 2025, by Warner Bros.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $316 million,
becoming both the best-reviewed and highest-grossing installment in the series.
In August 2025, it was announced that a sequel was in development.
The film explores themes of restaurant, gore, sequel, premonition, fate.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.